<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.cinetree" name="Cinetree" version="2.0.1" provider-name="Dimitri Kroon">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="inputstream.adaptive" version="19.0.7"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.31.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.7.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.codequick" version="1.0.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pytz" version="2023.3.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Films and documentaries from cinetree.nl (Benelux countries only, account required)</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Films en documentaires van cinetree.nl (Alleen in de Benelux, account vereist)</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">
      A privacy respecting way to watch free films or rent films from Dutch film platform cinetree.nl. Rental films can be rented directly by using your prepaid credit at Cinetree. If you prefer another payment method use the Cinetree website or the official Cinetree Android/Apple app to make the payment before watching the film on Kodi.[CR]This is an unofficial addon. It is not created or endorsed by Cinetree.
    </description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">
      Een privacy respecterende manier om gratis films te kijken, of films te huren van het Nederlandse filmplatform cinetree.nl. Huurfilms kunnen direct worden gehuurd met je prepaid tegoed bij Cinetree. Als je de voorkeur geeft aan een andere betaalmethode gebruik dan de Cinetree website of de officiële Cinetree Android/Apple app om de betaling te doen voordat je de film op Kodi bekijkt.[CR]Dit is een onofficiële addon. Het is niet gemaakt of goedgekeurd door Cinetree.
    </description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">
      This addon is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
    </disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">
      Deze addon is gedistribueerd in de hoop dat het nuttig zal zijn maar ZONDER ENIGE GARANTIE; zelfs zonder de impliciete garantie voor BRUIKBAARHEID VOOR EEN SPECIFIEK DOEL.
    </disclaimer>
    <language>nl</language>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=370761</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/dimkroon/cinetree-for-kodi</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/cinetree-logo.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <news>
- New logo image.
- Now possible to directly rent a film with your prepaid credit at Cinetree.
- Now possible to sort listings on the date the film was added to Cinetree.
- Sort Genre listings by using the context menu, instead of the side menu.
- The default sort order of all lists is now the same as the cinetree website.
- Added a main menu entry for Cinetree Originals.
- Added a main menu entry for short films.
- Added a menu entry to your saved watch list in 'My Films'.
- Added the possibility to add or remove films to your watch list by using the context menu.
- Properly display films as fully or partially watched.
- Sync the watched status of films watched on other devices.
- Better distinguish 'already watched' films from 'continue watching'.
- Added the possibility to remove films from 'already watched' and 'continue watching' by using the context menu in these lists.
- Fix: price info missing in the description of some rental films.
- Several other minor changes and changes under the hood.
    </news>
  </extension>
</addon>
